It's a short trip from zero... to hero.
Minutemen is a family, tv movie, comedy film directed by Lev L. Spiro.
When three high-school friends invent a time-machine, they decide to use it to go back
in time and prevent other youngsters from making humiliating mistakes.
Virgil Fox, played by Jason Dolley.
Zeke Thompson, played by Nicholas Braun.
Charlie Tuttle, played by Luke Benward.
Stephanie Jameson, played by Chelsea Kane.
Derek Beaugard, played by Steven R. McQueen.
Vice Principal Tolkan, played by J. P. Manoux.
Minutemen is a 2008 science-fiction Disney Channel Original Movie.
The movie was the most viewed program on American cable TV for the
week ending January 27, 2008, with 6.48 million viewers.
The film was written by John Killoran (writing the teleplay) and David Diamond
and David Weissman (writing the story) and directed by Lev L.
Spiro, who received a Directors Guild nomination for
Outstanding Achievement in Children's Programs for it.
Andrew Gunn, Ann Marie Sanderlin and Doug Sloan are the executive producers.
The movie was originally slated for release in March 2008, but the film
premiered on Disney Channel in United States on January 25.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.